<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="Develop OpenClovis model">
   <taskGroup name="Develop OpenClovis model" kind="sequence">
      <intro>
         Welcome to OpenClovis model development tutorial.
         This guide will walk you through the process of creating a new model, configuring HA, performing manageability, generate ASP ready model application source, build source, create images and deploy it to target machine.
         To assist you along the way, wizards and commands will be available for you to launch automatically.
      </intro>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Create model" skip="true">
         <param name="id" value="com.clovis.cw.tutorial.cheatsheet.createModel" />
         <intro>This guide will walk you through the process of setting up OpenClovis environment, creating a new model and getting familiar with the OpenClovis IDE.</intro>
         <onCompletion>Congratulations! You just created a model!</onCompletion>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Configure HA (High Availability)" skip="true">
         <param name="id" value="com.clovis.cw.tutorial.cheatsheet.configureHA" />
         <intro>This guide will walk you through the process of configuring components, associating resources for components and configuring AMF.</intro>
         <onCompletion>Congratulations! You just configured HA for the model!</onCompletion>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Perform manageability" skip="true">
         <param name="id" value="com.clovis.cw.tutorial.cheatsheet.performManageability" />
         <intro>This guide will walk you through the process of importing mibs, modeling resources, configuring alarms and associating resources for components.</intro>
         <onCompletion>Congratulations! You just performed manageability for the model!</onCompletion>
      </task>
      <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Build and deploy" skip="true">
         <param name="id" value="com.clovis.cw.tutorial.cheatsheet.buildAndDeploy" />
         <intro>This guide will walk you through the process of generating source code, customizing generated code, build, creating image, deploying image and running ASP.</intro>
         <onCompletion>Congratulations! You just built and deployed the model!</onCompletion>
      </task>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
